(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 19)
(PR Manager, Na Tae Hoon)
(Na Tae Hoon)
(6099)
(Na Tae Hoon, Welcome)
(Cheongma General Affairs Data,
Cheongma Vehicle Management)
(Cheongma PR Department:
Document Index)
(Weekly PR Report)
(PR Manager, Na Tae Hoon)
Ms. Joo.
Ms. Ko, what are you doing here?
And so late at night, too?
I was here for a meeting earlier,
and I left my phone behind.
Is that so?
For a second, I thought...
Well, if you left your phone,
that's understandable.
I can't live a single day
without my phone either.
Still, you should be relieved.
You're lucky I was the one
who found you.
What if it'd been someone else?
What would you have done
if you were accused of stealing?
Right?
Right.
So, how are you finding things
at the company?
Are you managing okay?
Yes, it's great.
You were pretty upset last time,
weren't you?
- Pardon?
- Looking back,
I was narrow-minded.
Once you've paid
your debt to society,
it's only right to accept you back.
I'm sure it was upsetting.
Not at all.
Well, thank you for saying so.
All right, then.
You should get going. It's late.
Right, I will.
What?
Were you really caught
by Director Joo?
So what happened?
Fortunately, she bought my excuse,
so I managed to smooth things over.
Well, that's a huge relief.
By the way,
what's Director Joo like?
Her reputation
at the company is good.
As the Chairman's right-hand woman,
she's highly capable
and easy to get along with.
Is that so?
Anyway, we need to be more careful.
I know.
If you caught her in the act,
you should've just called
the police.
Why didn't you?
It's more amusing this way.
She thinks she's being clever,
but she'll tire herself out.
Manager Na, you have
the countermeasures prepared, right?
Of course. Don't worry about that.
Good.
By the way,
CEO Kang has a friend
named Bae Jong Min.
He's a writer and a pundit.
Bae Jong Min?
Yes. See if you can dig up
some dirt on him.
It's always the intellectual types
who act so dignified...
that have the most to hide.
Understood.
Welcome, Chief Cha.
Thank you for having me over.
- This is for you.
- Goodness.
- Is this for me?
- Yes.
How did you know
I like these flowers?
Did you tell him?
No.
How did you know
Mom likes lisianthuses, Seok Jin?
I remember seeing it
in an online article once.
My goodness, you're so thoughtful.
Thank you, Seok Jin.
I'm glad you like them.
They smell wonderful, too.
Gosh, where's my head at?
Honey, Seok Jin's here.
Come say hello.
Right, welcome.
Since you're here,
how about a drink?
Sure.
Honey, could you get us
some drinks and snacks?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Wait.
You stay back.
Why, Mom?
Give them some space today.
Come on. Are you kidding me?
- Allow me.
- It's fine Let's keep it casual.
Here, have a drink.
Thank you.
So why are you here today?
Pardon?
I doubt you came here
just to chat with me.
So, what brings you here?
I wanted to know why you won't
give us your blessing.
You're telling me
you don't know why?
Is it because of my family?
Because we're no help
to Cheongma Group?
So you do know.
My one and only goal
is to make Cheongma...
the top company in the industry.
And to do that,
I desperately need connections.
You know that as well as I do.
There's no stronger alliance
than one made through marriage.
Then,
if I make Cheongma the top company
in the industry,
will you give us your blessing?
What did you say?
Within five years,
I'll make Cheongma the top company
in the industry.
To do that, we need to transition
into a total fashion company,
which is why I plan to launch
a new shoe brand.
If I succeed at all of that,
then will you...
reconsider?
All right.
Now it's my turn to ask a question.
Why make such
an impossible promise...
to marry Hae Ra
when you don't even love her?
I'm a man
who takes promises very seriously.
That's why I intend to keep
my promise to Hae Ra.
Is that the only reason?
Of course, succeeding you as CEO...
and growing Cheongma
into a global company...
is a challenge
I believe is well worth taking on.
You're a smooth talker,
I'll give you that.
But...
I can't stand people
who are all talk.
In any case,
successfully launch
the shoe brand first.
Yes, sir.
Here.
You must be busy
between your daily work...
and investigating
the department managers.
Isn't it exhausting?
This is nothing
compared to life in prison.
Oh, right. Of course.
Anyway, at this rate,
we should be able to find
the real killer by next week.
Well,
if everything goes
according to plan.
I'm suddenly getting nervous.
Why don't we go somewhere...
and grab a cold beer
before calling it a night?
Beer?
Why? You don't want to?
Well, it's...
I'm just a little tired.
Sorry about that.
I was only thinking of myself again.
Hey, we're almost home.
You should head in.
We're here.
I'll definitely
buy you that beer next time.
Okay. Don't worry about it.
Go on and get some rest.
Right. You get some rest too.
Sure.
You're such a fool.
Why are you just standing there?
Do my words mean nothing to you?
Didn't I tell you
to stop hanging out with Eun Seol?
You did.
And?
And I told you
that I don't care about rumors.
Hey, Seo Hyun Jae.
I'm not in the mood,
so just leave me alone.
I can't believe him.
Mom.
Why can't Uncle and Eun Seol
hang out together?
You don't need to know.
Why? Are you worried Uncle
and Eun Seol might start dating?
You shouldn't say things like that.
Wait a minute.
Do you even know
what that word means?
What? Dating?
Of course I do.
That's when you become
boyfriend and girlfriend.
Right?
Anyway, you shouldn't say
things like that.
Got it?
Is dating a bad thing?
Seo Teun Teun.
Fine.
- Are you a little drunk?
- I'm fine.
I'll be going now.
Okay. Did you have a good talk
with the CEO?
Yes, I guess.
Really?
Then, I'll see you at work tomorrow.
- Sure.
- Dad, Seok Jin's leaving.
Let him be.
He must be tired from drinking.
Let's go then. I'll drive you.
I can just call a driver.
I'm saying I'll be your driver.
I won't take long, Mom.
Sure.
Well, I'll be going now.
It's pretty dark out, so drive safe.
I will.
Goodness, you're in bed already?
Honey, Seok Jin just left.
Are you asleep?
Yes.
You say you're asleep,
but you just answered.
So?
What did you and Seok Jin
talk about?
Honey.
Whatever. I'm tired.
Hey, you're home.
You're still awake, Mom?
Yes.
I'm here too, Ms. Park.
Right. Hey.
Gosh, I'm tired.
Mr. Seok Jin,
I'm going to bed first.
Okay, sure. Good night, Mom.
Good night, Ms. Park.
So? What did you talk about
with my dad?
What else would I talk about
with the CEO besides work?
Didn't you tell him
you wanted to marry me?
Didn't you?
I did.
You did?
And what did he say?
You know the CEO is
against our marriage.
So just because he's against it,
you caved and told him
you wouldn't marry me?
Really?
Kang Hae Ra.
I'm going to try.
I'm going to work to get
the CEO's blessing for our marriage.
Really?
So, can you trust me and wait?
Of course.
You'd better not disappoint me.
And I won't disappoint you.
I get it.
How could I ever disappoint you?
I trust you.
But,
this time, when you're ready,
please tell me in good time.
(Cheongma)
Good morning.
Did everyone have a good weekend?
Yes. Did you have
a good weekend, Ms. Kang?
Did something good happen?
You seem to be in a good mood.
Do I?
Did you have a nice time
with Chief Cha?
That's enough
with the morning greetings.
Shall we start the meeting?
- Did you look into Bae Jong Min?
- Yes.
But there's nothing dirty about him
that's newsworthy.
What? No plagiarism allegations
or tax evasion charges?
No, ma'am.
What about his personal life?
Any trouble with women?
He's clean on that front too.
The only women he meets
are reporters.
Reporters?
Yes. There's one
female political reporter...
he hangs out with often.
They meet up for drinks sometimes,
but that's all.
Then link him with the reporter.
Pardon?
Is this your first day
working with me?
Are you dense or what?
Do I have to spell out
how to link him with the reporter?
I'm sorry. I'll take care of it.
Also, this...
What is it?
Professor Hong sent it to you.
I think it's a book.
- You can go.
- Yes, ma'am.
Who reads this stuff? Unbelievable.
What's this?
He must be desperate, seeing
as he's throwing money around.
Excuse me.
Me?
Who else would I be talking to?
Excuse me.
What?
Why are you so prickly?
Me? You think I'm prickly?
You don't know you're prickly?
In my entire life,
no one has ever said that to me.
Then you must not have any friends.
What did you say?
Well, that would explain
why you've never heard it.
For your information,
I have a lot of friends.
Whatever.
- What did you want?
- So, I...
Wait, what was I going to say?
You made me forget
by saying all that nonsense.
Now it's my fault you forgot
what you were going to say?
Anyway, I'm not prickly.
So stop making
a completely normal person sound strange.
Got it?
Who were you talking to for so long?
Mi Rae.
Who's Mi Rae?
Teun Teun's mom.
Then just say she's Teun Teun's mom.
What's with calling her Mi Rae?
Don't call her that.
Grandma, come on.
I'm just calling Mi Rae by her name.
What's wrong with that?
If I tell you not to, then don't.
I'm saying this for your own good.
Anyway, what were you two
talking about for so long?
How would I know?
She called me out of the blue,
only to forget
what she wanted to say.
What?
That shameless woman is making
a move on him, isn't she?
I need to give her a warning.
This won't do.
Mom, don't you even think
about saying anything harsh to her.
Don't forget
that we're living here for free.
As if. We pay our rent on time.
That's some interesting logic.
Anyone would think
you're the one paying the rent.
I remember now.
I was going to tell him
to keep his sister in line.
How could you forget that, Mi Rae?
Honey!
Did you see the article?
What article?
Haven't you heard about
Bae Jong Min's alleged affair?
What?
Oh, come on. That's ridiculous.
He's not that kind of person.
It must be someone
with the same name.
Look at this.
Still don't believe me?
(Writer and Pundit Bae Jong Min's
Alleged Affair with a Reporter)
Wait, hold on a second.
It's him, right? Unbelievable.
The phone is turned off.
You'll be connected to voicemail.
After the beep...
- He's not picking up?
- His phone is off.
Anyway, I've no intention of putting
Jong Min on our company's board,
so keep that in mind.
Now that this has happened,
I'm not going to insist
on him either.
- I'll look for someone else...
- No.
I'll take care of appointing
the new director myself.
Honey.
I'm the Chairman
of the Scholarship Foundation.
If you don't trust me that much,
you can vet them yourself later.
Who would be a good fit?
You still don't have anyone in mind?
I just assumed it'd be Bae Jong Min,
so I wasn't even thinking about it.
But who could've guessed
something this awful would happen?
Still, it's a relief we found out
before the director was appointed.
That's true.
So, is there anyone you'd recommend?
Well...
No one in my circle comes to mind.
How about someone from your clubs,
or anyone you know
who might be suitable?
My clubs?
Like your flower arrangement club.
You're in a calligraphy club too.
Since Director Han was a professor,
another former professor
would be a solid replacement.
Wait, there is one person.
Who?
Professor Hong Seok Gyu.
He retired last year.
He's in my calligraphy club.
I see. Then he sounds perfect.
Why didn't I think of him?
Thank you, Director Joo.
I knew I could count on you.
What a relief.
Then the only one left is...
The PR Manager.
The one we couldn't confirm
because of Director Joo?
Yes.
Do you think Manager Na Tae Hoon
is connected to the real killer?
Everyone else has an alibi,
so theoretically, yes.
He didn't seem like
that kind of person.
Actually,
I happened to run into him
the other day.
He seems like a really great guy
on the surface.
He's always so cheerful
when he says hello.
Yes, he was the same way with me.
But there's something...
Something feels off about him.
I saw it often in prison.
People who seem fake.
How's it going?
Have you found the real killer?
Not yet.
What's taking so long?
It'll be over soon.
Is there anything else
I can do to help?
No.
I just need to check on
one person tomorrow.
So tomorrow, we'll find out
who the real killer is?
Well, as long as
there are no surprises.
Gosh, my heart is racing.
Okay, then be careful
until the very end.
All right.
You scared me!
Do you want to give your son
a heart attack?
What's wrong with you?
What did I do?
Tell me. What's going on?
What do you mean?
Are you really not going to tell me?
Come on.
It's almost over,
so please wait a little longer.
I'll spill everything
when it's over,
whether you want
to hear it or not. Okay?
What the...
What on earth are they up to?
Everyone, let's go to lunch.
- Sure.
- Okay.
What should we get?
How about...
- Kongguksu?
- Kongguksu? Not really.
(PR Manager, Na Tae Hoon)
(Na Tae Hoon, Welcome)
(June 5: No scheduled appointments)
(Meeting with Hanbit's Kim Seong Sik,
2 p.m.)
What the heck?
Manager Na had a meeting
that day too?
Manager Na has an alibi too?
Yes. Apparently, he had a meeting
with a client that day.
How can that be?
If it isn't Manager Na either,
then we're out of suspects.
Exactly.
Where did we go wrong?
I really don't know.
Has everything we've done so far...
been for nothing?
Still, we have to check it out.
Director Joo, please say hello.
This is Professor Hong Seok Gyu,
who'll be our newest board member.
Is that right?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Joo Mi Ran.
Oh, right.
Hello.
Professor Hong, isn't this
your first time meeting her?
Yes, that's right.
Director Joo is someone
I couldn't do without.
Is that so?
You're too kind, ma'am.
She's the driving force
behind the foundation's affairs,
so if you have any questions,
you can just ask her.
Yes, I understand.
Excuse me for a moment.
Please, feel free to talk...
- among yourselves.
- Sure.
Yes, Professor.
Yes, of course.
Congratulations, Professor Hong.
Thank you.
I'll forever be
in your debt, Ms. Joo.
What is this?
Are you kidding me with that?
It's not what you think. This is...
I don't need anything else.
You just need to be on my side.
Do you understand?
Oh, of course. Without a doubt.
Don't you worry about that.
Come in.
Hello, I'm Ko Eun Seol.
I called earlier.
You're Team Leader Kim Seong Sik,
correct?
Yes, that's me.
Please, have a seat.
You wanted to inquire
about a new product launch event?
Yes, I was hoping to get a quote.
What size event are you thinking of?
The details are
in the materials I sent.
You'll know when you see them.
I see.
I'm sorry,
but my throat is a bit dry.
Could I have something to drink?
Oh, where are my manners?
Please wait a moment.
(2 p.m., Meeting with
Manager Na Tae Hoon from Cheongma)
The other entries are written
in the exact same ink.
(2 p.m., Meeting with
Manager Na Tae Hoon from Cheongma)
So why does this day's entry...
The handwriting...
(2 p.m., Meeting with
Manager Na Tae Hoon from Cheongma)
Then...
(Meeting with Hanbit's Kim Seong Sik,
2 p.m.)
What the heck?
Manager Na had a meeting
that day too?
Was this added for me to see?
(A Trap Called Desire)
I'm trusting you on this.
I love you.
I knew they were spending
a lot of time together.
I didn't realize they were an item.
What's your relationship
with Eun Seol?
Does what we have
seem that special to you?
Pig's feet? Come on. Have you
ever seen trotters this sexy?
Pig's feet?
I'm literally the Chairman
of the scholarship foundation,
so why can't I appoint
a single director the way I want?
Director Joo,
you need to take one for the team.
Was it your recommendation,
Director Joo?
Are you that dense?
What exactly have you been doing?
So what do we do now?
For the first time in ten years,
they're going to be scared
because of me.
Can't I enjoy that just a bit?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)